Guide to the Gordon Moore Papers M1965
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Chronological Files, 1958-2003
  - Sub-Series IV: Calendars, 1974-1999
    - Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 105, Folder 11], 1981 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - BusinessWeek Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 105, Folder 12], 1981 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - BusinessWeek Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 105, Folder 13], 1982 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - BusinessWeek Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 105, Folder 14], 1983 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 105, Folder 15], 1984 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Success Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 105, Folder 16], 1985 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - The 1986 Fortune Diary [Originally in Box 105, Folder 17] (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - The 1987 Fortune Diary [Originally in Box 106, Folder 1] (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Singapore Business Diary [Originally in Box 106, Folder 2], 1988 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - The Wellness Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 3], 1989 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - The Wellness Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 4], 1990 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - The Wellness Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 5], 1991 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 6], 1992 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Weekly-Minder Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 7], 1993 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Weekly-Minder Weekly Planner, Correspondence re: Directory Lists, Payroll Schedule, Sales Office Lists, Executive Staff Meeting Agendas, Schedules, Brochure [Originally in Box 106, Folder 8], 1994 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Weekly-Minder Weekly Planner, Correspondence re: Executive Staff Meeting Agendas, Schedules [Originally in Box 106, Folder 9], 1995 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Weekly Planner, Correspondence re: Executive Staff Meeting Agendas, Schedules, Graphs [Originally in Box 106, Folder 10], 1996 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 11], 1997 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 12], 1998 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 13], 1999 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 14], 1982 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 15], 1983 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 16], 1984 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 17], 1985 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 18], 1986 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 19], 1987 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 20], 1988 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 21], 1989 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 22], 1991 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 23], 1992 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 24], 1995 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 25], 1996 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 26], 1997 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 27], 1998 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Pocket Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 106, Folder 28], 1999 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Memopad re: Economic Conference [Originally in Box 106, Folder 29], 1992 (Box 96, Folder 9)
- Series 3: Alphabetical Files, 1968-2001
  The alphabetical section is comprised of material from companies, universities, and organizations affiliated with Moore. Items include correspondence, minutes, programs, and brochures. Other subjects include people (i.e. Robert Noyce, Andrew Grove), biographical material, economic data, trade policy, and litigations. Some Intel related files are mixed in with the alphabetical files that include budget, customer correspondence, industry statistics, and awards. There are multiple files related to California Institute of Technology, Varian Associates, and Transamerica Inc. Gordon Moore personal files are also located in this series. The last four boxes in this series house greeting cards, business cards, a rolodex, and oversized material from the chronological files and alphabetical files.
  - Applied Technology Institute for Microelectronics, SJSU, School of Engineering (4 of 4) [Originally in Box 108, Folder 1], 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Chaunce Arlie Beane, Jr., President of Eureka Production Corp. and General Partner of XAN, Ltd. - Correspondence re: Investment in Peten Petroleum S.A., Reports [Originally in Box 108, Folder 4], 1990-1994 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Biography of Robert N. Noyce - Index Cards, Pamphlets, Photocopies of Biographical Articles [Originally in Box 108, Folder 5], 1978-1982 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Biographical Miscellaneous Articles re: Andrew Grove, Craig Barrett, Dov Frohman, Edward Gelbach, Laurence Hootnick, Dave House, H.T. Chua, Leslie Vadasz, Marcian Hoff, Richard Bohn [Originally in Box 108, Folder 6], undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - BRIE (Berkeley Roundtable on the International Economy) - Correspondence, Reports re: The Competitive Semiconductor Manufacturing Human Resources Project [Originally in Box 108, Folder 7], 1993-1996 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Intel Corp. Presentation Slides from Andrew Grove re: Montgomery Securities, District Manager’s Presentation (1 of 4) [Originally in Box 109, Folder 2], 1986-1989 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - California-Israel Exchange, State of California - Board of Directors Meeting Agendas, Notes, Correspondence re: State of California Task Force, Governor’s Trade Mission to Israel, SNAP Technology (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 111, Folder 3], 1992 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - California-Israel Exchange, State of California - Newsletter, Link: Israeli Business and Technology Magazine, Board of Directors Meeting Agendas, Biographical Article re: Governor Pete Wilson, Notes, Correspondence (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 111, Folder 4], 1992- 1996 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Caltech - Jet Propulsion Laboratory Annual Reports, Agenda, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 111, Folder 5], 1985-1991 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Caltech - Correspondence, Agenda re: Board of Trustees Meetings, Presentation Slides re: Jet Propulsion Laboratory, Minutes [Originally in Box 112, Folder 1], 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Caltech - Correspondence re: Awards, Agenda for Jet Propulsion Laboratory Meeting of Trustees’ Committee, Notes, Presentation Slides, Resumes [Originally in Box 112, Folder 2], January-April 1991-1994 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Caltech - Correspondence re: Space Policy and Program Leadership, Booklet re: Financials, Agendas, Minutes re: Board of Trustees Meeting in Palm Springs, Articles re: Appointment as Chairman, Notes [Originally in Box 112, Folder 3], 1993 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Caltech - Correspondence, Invitations re: Event with Carver Mead, The Gordon and Betty Moore Professor of Engineering and Applied Science at Fairmont Hotel [Originally in Box 112, Folder 4], 1993 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Caltech Division of Engineering and Applied Science Visiting Committee Binder with Presentation Slides, Agenda, Notes, Booklet re: Graduate Aeronautical Laboratories Caltech (GALCIT) [Originally in Box 112, Folder 5], 1994 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Caltech Correspondence, Reports re: Capital Budget, Financial Statements, Endowment Pool, Preliminary Official Statement for Series 1991 Bonds (Background Documents for February 1994 Meeting) [Originally in Box 112, Folder 6], 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Caltech Investment Committee Binder re: Presentation Slides, Beckman Foundation Report, Nominating Committee Agenda and Reports [Originally in Box 113, Folder 1], 1994 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Caltech Correspondence, Agenda re: Board of Trustees Meeting, Minutes, Reports on Class of 1994, Article, Notes, Booklet re: Financials, Annual Reports (1991-1994) [Originally in Box 113, Folder 2] (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Caltech - Correspondence re: JPL-Caltech Political Action Plan, Moore Laboratory, Agenda, Minutes re: Board of Trustees Meeting, Presentation Slides, Booklets re: Financials, Commencement Speeches, Graphs, Articles re: Jet Propulsion Laboratory (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 113, Folder 3], 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Caltech - Correspondence, Minutes, Agendas, Notes, Division of Engineering and Applied Science Visiting Committee Report (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 113, Folder 4], 1994 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Caltech - Correspondence, Minutes, Agendas, Booklet re: Financials [Originally in Box 114, Folder 1], 1994 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Caltech Engineering and Science Magazines re: The Accidental Entrepreneur Article [Originally in Box 114, Folder 2], 1994 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Caltech - Correspondence, Agenda re: Board of Trustees Meetings, Minutes, Report to Audit Committee, Financial Statement, Graphs [Originally in Box 114, Folder 3], 1995 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Caltech - Correspondence, Agenda re: Board of Trustees Meetings, Minutes, Booklet re: Financials [Originally in Box 114, Folder 4], 1995 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Caltech Investment Committee Meeting and Executive Committee Meeting Minutes [Originally in Box 114, Folder 5], 1995 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Caltech Correspondence re: Patent License Agreements, Agenda, Minutes re: Board of Trustees Meetings [Originally in Box 114, Folder 6], 1996 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Caltech Correspondence, Agenda re: Board of Trustees Meeting, Minutes, Booklet re: Credit Review, Financials [Originally in Box 114, Folder 7], 1996 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Caltech - Board of Trustees Meeting Schedule [Originally in Box 114, Folder 8], 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Caltech Biological Sciences Initiative Committee Meeting Minutes, Gift Committee Handbook [Originally in Box 114, Folder 9], 1997 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Caltech Presidential Search - Correspondence, Contract re: David Baltimore, Articles [Originally in Box 114, Folder 10], 1995-1998 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Caltech Rosters (1996-1999), Agenda, Minutes re: Board Meetings [Originally in Box 115, Folder 1], 1997 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Caltech Corporate Bylaws [Originally in Box 115, Folder 2], 1997 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Caltech Board of Trustees Officers and Committees, Booklet re: Resumes of Potential Board Candidates [Originally in Box 115, Folder 3], 1995-1997 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Caltech Correspondence re: Board of Trustees and Members, Curriculum, Revenue Bonds Series 1994, Notes, Annual Report Draft, Brochure re: Voyager Spacecraft, Presentation by David Goodstein, Financial Report for National Academies’ Corp. Beckman Center, Grievance Form, Meeting Agenda [Originally in Box 115, Folder 4], 1994-1997 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Caltech Division of Engineering and Applied Science Visiting Committee Meeting Report [Originally in Box 115, Folder 5], 1994 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Caltech Board of Trustees Meetings - Correspondence, Agenda, Minutes, News Articles, Roster, Annual Report, Booklet re: Jet Propulsion Laboratory [Originally in Box 115, Folder 6], 1988-1992 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Caltech Board of Trustees - Correspondence re: Trustees Meeting and Presentation by Gordon Moore, Research Paper re: National Symposium on Reinventing the Research University by Simon Ramo, Agendas, Bylaws Draft, Minutes, Notes, Articles re: Graduate Schools [Originally in Box 116, Folder 1], 1994-1995 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Caltech Board of Trustees - Correspondence, Notes, Report re: Effective Asset Allocation, Agendas, Roster, Minutes [Originally in Box 116, Folder 2], 1995 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Caltech Board of Trustees - Correspondence, Commencement Transcript, Agendas, Minutes, Bylaws Draft [Originally in Box 116, Folder 3], 1997 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Caltech Jet Propulsion Lab (NASA) - Presentation Slides re: Microelectronics Systems Vision by Leon Alkalai, Annual Reports, Brochures re: Project Design Center, Flight System Testbed, The New Millennium Program Plan [Originally in Box 116, Folder 4], 1993-1995 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Caltech Jet Propulsion Lab Committee Meeting - Agendas, Notes, Correspondence, Articles, Strategic Plan [Originally in Box 116, Folder 5], 1995 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Caltech Board of Trustees Nominating Committee Binder - Correspondence, Budget Plan, Agenda [Originally in Box 116, Folder 6], 1994 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Caltech Jet Propulsion Lab - Annual Reports, Booklets re: Highlights, Meeting Agendas (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 116, Folder 7], 1988-1989 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Caltech Jet Propulsion Lab - Booklets re: Meeting Agendas, Agenda, Minutes, Bylaws Draft (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 117, Folder 1], 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Caltech Board of Trustees Meeting - Reports, Minutes, Notes, Booklet re: Bridge Fund, Caltech [Originally in Box 117, Folder 2], 1994 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Caltech Budget Booklet [Originally in Box 117, Folder 3], 1998 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Mellon University - Correspondence with Dan Holbrook, Interview Transcript, Photocopies of Fairchild Semiconductor Material [Originally in Box 117, Folder 6], 1994 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - The Center for Economic Policy Research, Stanford University - Board Meeting Agenda, Minutes, Correspondence, Booklets, Newsletters, SU Campus Report Newspaper [Originally in Box 118, Folder 1], 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Charity Requests - Correspondence [Originally in Box 118, Folder 2], 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Compaq Computer Corp. - Correspondence, Meeting Minutes [Originally in Box 118, Folder 3], 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Conservation International - Correspondence re: Board Meeting Minutes, Brochures, Project, Rapid Assessment Program Scientific Team, Four Macaws Print [Originally in Box 118, Folder 4], 1992-1997 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Conservation International - Kayapo Trip Letter [Originally in Box 118, Folder 5], 1994 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Conservation International - Articles, Policy Papers, Annual and Progress Reports, Notes, Pamphlets, Maps (1 of 3) [Originally in Box 118, Folder 6], 1993-1997 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Conservation International - Articles, Policy Papers, Annual and Progress Reports, Notes, Pamphlets, Maps (2 of 3) [Originally in Box 118, Folder 7], 1993-1997 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Conservation International Science Advisory Committee - Correspondence re: Intel/CI/UNESCO Partnership, Minutes and Agenda re: Executive Committee, Reports, Maps (3 of 3) [Originally in Box 119, Folder 1], 1989-1997 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Conservation International, Development Committee Meeting Binder - Agenda, Minutes [Originally in Box 119, Folder 2], June 1993 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Council on Competitiveness - Correspondence, Technology Reports re: Japanese Technology, National Technology Priorities Project, Technology Priorities for America’s Future (1 of 6) [Originally in Box 119, Folder 3], 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Council on Competitiveness - Correspondence, Technology Reports re: Capital Choices, Competitiveness Strategy for America, Roadmap for Results (2 of 6) [Originally in Box 119, Folder 4], 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Council on Competitiveness - Correspondence, Memorandums, Notes, Article, Technology Reports re: Reinventing Research and Development, Competitive Index (3 of 6) [Originally in Box 120, Folder 1], 1994 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Council on Competitiveness - Correspondence, Memorandums, Notes, Article, Report re: Technology Priorities for America’s Future (4 of 6) [Originally in Box 120, Folder 2], 1994 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Council on Competitiveness - Correspondence, Technology Reports re: Automotive and Pharmaceutical Industries, Endless Frontier-Limited Resources (5 of 6) [Originally in Box 120, Folder 3], 1995 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Council on Competitiveness - Correspondence, Technology Reports re: Reinventing R&D, Automotive and Pharmaceutical Industries, Endless Frontier-Finite Resources (6 of 6) [Originally in Box 120, Folder 4], 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Economic Data - Correspondence, Articles, Graphs re: Industry Capacity, Intel Financials, Trade Policy, Cost Systems, Industry Statistics [Originally in Box 121, Folder 9], 1984-1989 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Economic Strategy Institute - Correspondence, Publications Catalog, Articles, Booklets re: Foreign Regulations, Telecommunications Services Industry, Free Trade (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 122, Folder 1], 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Economic Strategy Institute - Correspondence, Publications Catalog, Articles, Booklets re: Product Liability, Liability Reform, Japanese Policy, Multinational Corporations (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 122, Folder 2], 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - TELOS (The Electronic Library of Science) - Manuscripts of The Microprocessor, A Biography by Michael Malone, Correspondence, Pamphlet [Originally in Box 122, Folder 3], 1995 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Exploratorium Awards Dinner, San Francisco - Correspondence, Receipts (originally in National Science and Technology Medals Foundation Folder) [Originally in Box 122, Folder 4], 1983-1985 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Gilead Sciences Inc. - Notebook re: Compensation Review, Correspondence re: Stock, Directors’ Questionnaire, SEC Form 10-K, Evaluation Criteria for Board Members [Originally in Box 122, Folder 7], 1997-1998 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Gilead Sciences Inc. - US Securities and Exchange Commission Form 4, Form S-8, Form 10-K [Originally in Box 123, Folder 1], 1995-1997 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Gilead Sciences Inc. - Annual Reports, Presentation Slides, Reports, Articles, Agenda, Minutes [Originally in Box 123, Folder 2], 1991-1997 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Gilead Sciences Inc. - Annual Reports, Presentation Slides, Booklets re: Operating Plan, Reports [Originally in Box 123, Folder 3], 1996-1997 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Gilead Sciences Inc. - Correspondence, Articles, Agenda, Minutes, SEC Form 10-K, Notes, Annual Report [Originally in Box 123, Folder 4], 1997 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Government Affairs Position Papers re: Environment, Financial, Human Resources, Legal Reform, Trade, Telecommunications Policy, National Technology Policy [Originally in Box 123, Folder 5], 1995 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Governor Pete Wilson Campaign - Correspondence, Notes re: Roundtable Luncheon with Silicon Valley Advisory Group [Originally in Box 123, Folder 6], 1994 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Stephen Hawking, University of Cambridge - Agenda re: Stephen Hawking Lecture/Dinner, Correspondence, Presentation re: Life in the Universe by Stephen Hawking [Originally in Box 123, Folder 7], 1996 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - History of Semiconductor Industry (located in Economic Data folder) - Correspondence, Articles re: Silicon Valley, Intel Corp., US Semiconductor Industry, Fairchild Corp, Inteleads Newsletter, Avnet Inc. Annual Report, Booklets re: California’s Leading Companies, Research Paper re: The New Industrial Revolution by Andrew Grove (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 124, Folder 1], 1981-1990 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - History of Semiconductor Industry (located in Economic Data folder) - Presentation by Chih-Tang Sah re: Evolution of MOS transistor, EDN Magazine re: Microprocessors, Intel Newsletter (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 124, Folder 2], 1981-1988 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Horatio Alger Association of Distinguished Americans, Inc. - Correspondence re: Horatio Alger Award, Booklets, Biennial Reports, Postcards [Originally in Box 124, Folder 3], 1995-1996 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Horatio Alger Association of Distinguished Americans, Inc. - Correspondence, Booklets, Programs, Reports, The Forum Newsletters, Pamphlets (books) [Originally in Box 124, Folder 4], 1996-1997 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Industrial Security - Correspondence, Department of Defense Briefings re: Federal Criminal Statutes, Security Clearance Form re: Intel Systems II, Standard Practice Procedure Manual for Safeguarding Classified Information [Originally in Box 125, Folder 1], 1986-1988 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - IIE (Institute of International Education) William H. Draper III, Chairman - Correspondence, Brochure, Annual Report [Originally in Box 125, Folder 4], 1995-1996 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Intel Corp. Industry Statistics - Dataquest Reports re: Market Share Estimates, MOS Memory Forecasts and Data, Spreadsheets (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 125, Folder 6], 1985-1989 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Intel Corp. Industry Statistics - Dataquest Reports re: US Demographics, Preliminary Worldwide Market Share Estimates, Dataquest Research Newsletters, Semiconductor Equipment and Materials Institute Executive Summary Reports (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 126, Folder 1], 1990-1992 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Intel Corp. - Internal Publications, Intel Leads Quarterly, Intel Insight [Originally in Box 173], 1996 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Intel Networking and Management Press Coverage – Newsclipping Booklet [Originally in Box 173], 1996 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Intel Quality Awards - Application, Scoring Guidelines, Program, Performance Report [Originally in Box 127, Folder 4], 1994 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - T Comp News [Originally in Box 173], 1986 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Intel Corp. Bound Management Letters, [Originally in Box 127, Folder 6], 1986, 1988, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Intel Corp. Corporate Gifts - Note [Originally in Box 128, Folder 3], undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Intel Corp. Firsts and Major Milestones - History, Timeline [Originally in Box 128, Folder 10], 1968-1983 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Intel Corp. Travel Service - Handbook Binder: Directory, Reservation Process, International, Planning, Finance, Vacation, Policies [Originally in Box 128, Folder 14], undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Intel Corp. Publications [Originally in Box 173], 1996 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - News clippings, Photocopied Articles, Correspondence, Interview Transcript re: Gordon E. Moore, and Intel Corp., Japanese Competitors, Chinese Technology, Booklet on Santa Clara Recreational Activities [Originally in Box 129, Folder 1], 1987-1992 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Investments - Disclosure Agreement re: I-STAT Corp. Investment, Receipts, Correspondence, Quantum Group, Inc. Business Plan, Indemnity Agreement re: Varian Associates, Agreement of Limited Partnership with Southgreen Partners, Memorandum re: Venture Growth Associates, California Golden Seals, Hockey Club Ltd Promissory Note (originally in National Science and Technology Medals Foundation Folder) [Originally in Box 129, Folder 9], 1979-1989 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Ireland White House Conference on Trade and Investment - The Irish Times Newspaper [Originally in Box 129, Folder 10], 1995 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Ireland’s Historic Science Center - Correspondence re: Council, Pamphlet [Originally in Box 129, Folder 11], 1994 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Japanese Consumer Electronics - Newsletters, Presentation Slides, Booklet re: Sharp Corp. [Originally in Box 130, Folder 1], 1990 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Joint Venture: Silicon Valley Inc. - Correspondence, Advisory Board Meeting Minutes, Agenda, Work Plans for Phase I and II (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 130, Folder 3], 1992 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Litigations - Correspondence, Deposition Transcripts, Testimony re: Intel Corp. vs. Advanced Micro Devices Corp. (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 131, Folder 2], 1990-1993 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Litigations - Correspondence, Depositions re: Shareholders Class Action Suit (Eisenstadts vs Intel Corp.); Intel Corp. vs. Walentas-Phoenix Corp; Hughes Aircraft Company vs. Intel Corp (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 131, Folder 3], 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Litigations - Correspondence, Depositions re: Chips and Technologies Inc and Texas Instruments Inc. [Originally in Box 131, Folder 4], 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 3)